We have a bit of time before your
appointment with the principal.
Did you want to stop anywhere?
It's fine.
I'll show up early for a change.
Stop the car.
Huh? Right here?
Go on ahead.
Huh? A-Are you testing me?
You're not going to hit me if
I actually go on ahead, are you?
Just what do you think I am?
In that case...
Now...
Who are you?
That was easier than I expected.
Who are you...
calling easy?
Brat.
He's a cursed spirit, but he
can communicate clearly.
And the sheer amount of cursed energy...
An unregistered special-grade?
He's likely stronger than Sukuna currently is.
Special-grades are classified
as such because they're special.
Having them pop up this frequently
throws everything off.
Did I wound your pride?
Nope.
I'm starting to find this fun.
Jujutsu Kaisen
Episode 7:  Assault
Finding this fun, you say?
No sense of danger at all.
He chose a place devoid of people?
No, he was avoiding other
sorcerers coming to back me up.
Ember Insects!
Well, if you're coming
after me, you're right...
about having no sense of danger.
What happens if this hits me?
Sound?
A two-stage attack of sound and explosions?
That's clever.
There's more!
That's all it took?
I took a look for myself, and it was
just an overestimation by the weak.
That human was just as fragile as the rest.
He wasn't living a life of truth.
It's all so nauseatingly repulsive.
I'm going to go spread real strength,
the truth, through death.
We just went over this a moment ago.
Can't you even learn? Ugh, this smoke...
What's the meaning of this?
To put it simply, you didn't hit me.
Impossible. That wasn't like before.
I know I touched you and killed you.
You touched the "Infinity" that
exists between you and me.
I'll show you.
Put your hand out.
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
No hostility? I guess I'll see what it's about.
See?
I can't touch him?
It stops just before him.
This is Infinity?
You're not exactly stopped,
but the closer you get, the slower you go.
So, what now?
We could just shake
hands like this, you know.
I refuse.
Don't be shy, now.
You're making me embarrassed, too.
Damn you!
He's fast!
It's not just a blow
strengthened by cursed energy!
What is this?!
I don't get it!
I have to know!
There's still more!
Infinity exists everywhere.
My jujutsu just brings it forward in reality.
Convergence, divergence...
What do you think happens
when one touchs this void?
Cursed Technique Reversal: Red.
Oh, this is perfect.
You can try,
but you'll die, Jougo.
It wasn't just talk.
No matter. If I can't hit him,
I'll just drag him into my Domain.
Where did he go?
Sorry about that.
Where the heck?! Hey, where are we?!
Were you waiting?
That's...
Sukuna's vessel?!
This is Itadori Yuuji-kun,
and he's here to watch.
Mt. Fuji! His head's Mt. Fuji!
I'll protect you.
I'll never leave you.
Sam...
Wow, he learns surprisingly quick.
Come on.
Yuuji.
Gojou-sensei?
Talking to him doesn't
cause a problem, either.
You need something?
Looks like we'll be able to increase his output
quickly and move on to the next stage soon.
We're heading out, Yuuji.
Huh?
It's an extracurricular lesson.
I'm going to teach you about the pinnacle
of jujutsu battles, Domain Expansion.
Why aren't we sinking?!
Sensei, I was at the school
just ten seconds ago, right?
What's going on here?
Oh, we warped here.
He has no intention of explaining.
Sukuna's vessel...
So he really is alive.
You have to render Gojou
Satoru incapable of fighting.
The second is to get Ryoumen Sukuna
and Itadori Yuuji on your side.
I can't kill Itadori due to our future plans...
Has he caught on to our goals?
What's the brat for? He a shield?
A shield? No, no.
I told you, he's here to watch.
I'm in the middle of teaching
this boy lots of things.
Don't worry about him. Just keep fighting.
Bringing in someone who will slow
you down just makes you a fool.
It'll be fine. After all...
you're weak.
Don't underestimate me, brat!
I'm going to enjoy swallowing
up that smug face of yours!
This guy...
is weak?
He's way more monstrous than any of
the monsters I've encountered so far!
You'll be fine.
Just stay close to me.
Domain Expansion!
Wh-What is this?!
Coffin of the Iron Mountain!
Jujutsu Kaisen
Wh-What is this?!
This is Domain Expansion.
You use cursed energy to
construct an Innate Domain
Ow, hot!
Hot, hot, hot!
imbued with a cursed technique
in your surroundings.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
What you all experienced at
the juvenile detention center
was an incomplete Domain that hadn't
been imbued with any cursed techniques.
If that had been a proper Domain,
all of you first-years would have died.
I think Megumi understood that.
Spreading out a Domain
consumes a ton of energy,
but its merits are worth the cost.
One such benefit is the boost to
stats due to environmental factors.
Oh!
Like buffs in video games!
Another is...
Most sorcerers would have burned to ash
the moment they entered my Domain!
...that the techniques imbued in the Domain
are guaranteed to hit within that Domain.
Guaranteed?!
Guaranteed.
But don't worry. There are
several ways to deal with it.
You can take the hit using a
cursed technique, like just now, or...
I don't really recommend this one,
but you can go outside the Domain.
That's usually impossible.
You can also...
If I neutralize that Infinity
of yours with a dense Domain,
then my techniques will reach you.
Yeah, they'll hit.
Huh? Infinity?
Give me the Prison Realm!
I'll add it to my collection.
I came here half in jest.
I thought I wouldn't care if I couldn't kill him.
But having this difference
between us thrust in my face...
On my pride as a cursed spirit,
as the new humanity,
this is completely unacceptable!
The most effective way to deal with a Domain
is to lay out your own Domain.
When two Domains are
laid out at the same time,
the more refined one
will dominate that space.
Though, sometimes, compatibility and
the amount of cursed energy are factors.
There won't even be ashes
left of you, Gojou Satoru!
Domain Expansion:
Infinite Void.
What just happened?
Was my Domain overwhelmed?
I can't see anything.
I can't feel anything.
No...
I can see everything!
I can feel everything!
But the information is never complete...
So I can't do anything!
This is the inner world of Limitless.
Perception, communication...
Every action involved in living is forcibly
carried out an infinite number of times.
It's ironic, isn't it?
When granted everything,
you can't do anything...
but just die peacefully.
But I have questions I want to ask you,
so I'm letting you off the hook with this.
Now, who told you to come after me?
He really is the strongest jujutsu sorcerer!
As a living organism,
he's on another level!
Oh, dear.
What now?
Will you rescue him?
I can't let people from the school see
my face, so I'll be going home now.
If you want to save him,
go ahead and save him.
Though I don't know if your
kind have such emotions.
We do. We're the true humans, after all.
Quite the statement for
a cursed spirit to make.
You don't seem like the type to act on orders.
Was something good supposed
to happen if you killed me?
Regardless, I want to know. Who was it?
Come on, just tell me already.
Like I'd ever tell you, brat!
You sure you should be saying that?
Damn you!
Hurry up and tell me, or I'll exorcise you.
Of course, I'll do that either way.
Wait, curses are capable
of holding conversations?
It seemed so normal, I overlooked it.
Wow!
Flowers!
Pretty!
That is a curse, right?
It's stripping away my will to fight.
Sensei, I'll be fine!
Go after him!
Sorry, I lied! Help!
Wow.
He got away.
He's good at hiding his presence.
He's way creepier than Volcano Head.
I'm sorry about that.
They managed to escape because of me.
Though you're the one who brought me here, right?
- Yuuji
I'm sorry about that.
So cursed spirits of that level
are forming a faction now?
They managed to escape because of me.
Though you're the one
who brought me here, right?
This is getting interesting.
Yuuji.
I want you—or rather, everyone—
to become strong enough to beat that.
Huh? Beat that?
It's better to have a concrete goal, right?
Man, I'm glad brought you here.
I had no idea what was going on, though.
Are you serious?
Now that we've set your goal,
all that's left is to pursue it.
We'll speed up the schedule a bit.
For the next month, you'll be
watching movies and fighting me.
Fighting you?!
Will I still be alive a month from now?
After that, it's practical combat.
You'll take on and complete
several harder missions.
You'll learn the basics
and how to apply them,
and then you'll show them off
at the exchange event.
Hey, Sensei!
Yes, Yuuji-kun?
What's the exchange event?
I didn't tell you?
He's late!
Sure is peaceful here.
How's Jougo doing, Getou?
On death's door.
Hanami stepped in to save him,
so he'll probably be fine.
How irresponsible.
You're the one who egged him on.
Heavens, no.
I tried to stop him.
Speak of the devil.
Jougo, Hanami.
Glad to see you're safe.
How can you say that when you see me like this?!
You're lucky you got off with just that.
Why, you...
I think you understand now...
So we'll go about sealing Gojou Satoru
at the appropriate time,
in the appropriate place, once we've secured our advantage over him.
We'll carry it out on October 31st in Shibuya.
I'll contact you with more details later.
Good enough, Mahito?
Cloud Giant
No objections here.
Let's be cunning about this.
Like curses should.
Like humans should.
Juju Stroll
One, two, three, four...
What are you doing?
Brazilian calisthenics.
Three, four...
I think we're nice and warmed up now.
Yeah.
What are you two planning to do?
Getou-kun!
Shoot!
Mahito-kun!
Overhead!
Shoot!
I'm gonna kill these two later!
Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
Episode 8:
Boredom